未。
發現。
立法會主席。
主席。
19， our first report. This is
on behalf of the Public Accounts Committee.
Mr. President， on behalf of the，支援等等。
I have the honour to table our report number seventy five A.
章節二， on government's effort in tackling shoreline refuse.
石禮謙議員就政府賬目委員會第七十五A。
This is the committee's second report in response to the director of audit report number seventy five.
The public hearings on these chapters have previously been postponed in view of the convict.
發言，石禮謙議員就政府帳目委員會第七十五號A報告書向本會發言，石禮謙議員。
Chapter four on efforts on the Home Affairs Department in facilitating building management.
Report number seventy five, which focuses on the other seven chapters, were tabled in the council on twenty four February this year.
It contains our conclusions and recommendations on Chapter One, on collection and removal of marine refuse by the Marine Department.
The committee urges Marine Department.
and to operate four marine refuse collection points.
collection and removal of marine refuse by the marine department.
percent of the overall weight of marine refuse as reported by the marine department, C.O.R.S.
我會 now highlight some of the committee's conclusions and recommendations in our report number seventy five A.
委員會表達嚴重 concern，，that the marine department has failed to ensure the quantity.
委員會建議，作為所有海洋廢物由海洋部門承包商收集後，將會被處置。
Of marine refuse collected is reasonably accurate and can truly reflect its performance in tackling marine refuse.
to step up the monitoring of the contractor's performance and exercise its right under the contract to impose penalty against the contractor as and when appropriate.
The weight of marine refuse collected, as reported in Marine's Department controlling officers' report, calls was only an estimated based on the number of bags of such refuse collected by the Marine's Department's contractor.
In managing its contract for marine refuse cleansing and disposal service, Marine Department has not enforced the penalty provisions under the contract against the contractor for its unauthorised subcontracting arrangements.
Furthermore, Marine Department has not, in accordance with the relevant contract provisions, taken any follow-up action in respect of the contractor's failures to perform in marine refuse cleansing work at a number of typhoon shelters and promenades.
From two hundred and one two to two hundred and one nine, the overall weight of the municipal solid waste, which includes among others marine refuse disposed of by the marine department contractor at designated disposal facilities, was a meagre nineteen point nine.
歐洲。
主席，最近。
委員會 urge。
質詢第一行質詢陳佩然議員。
Building management matters. The committee urges the HAD.
Effort of the Home Affairs Department in facilitating building management.
Failing support. Last but not least, to the staff of the Legislative Chamber. Thank you.
The last subject is relating to the efforts of the HAD in facilitating.
Building management, HAD is tasked with assisting owners of private buildings to form owners' corporations and deal with.
要更積極，並擔任領先角色，協調相關努力，以迅速且有效，地評估私有建築所有者。
Building management matters. However, in its reply to the committee's question regarding the actions initiated by the administration to resolve building safety and fire safety,
委員會表達嚴重 concern about HAD lack of initiative in coordinating the efforts of the various departments in providing support services to owners of private building.
problems as such on behalf of the owners of private building. HAD advised that since it was not the department in charge of the relevant policy areas and legislation, it did not possess the relevant information.
That the environmental bureau has not demonstrated it that it had exerted its best effort to steer the working group towards maximising the collaborative efforts made by member departments in tackling shoreline refuse.
of at the designated disposal facilities, marine department should consider using actual weights of marine refuse disposed of for reporting in its CORs. The committee expresses grave concern about the marine department' ineffective.
政府努力在 tackles shoreline refuse， The Environmental Bureau coordinated the establishment of an interdepartmental working group， the working group， to enhance the collaborative efforts among relevant departments in tackling marine refuse.
However, no performance target or timetable for improving the cleanliness of shorelines have been set by the working group, and there are some areas along the Hong Kong shorelines which do not fall within the purview of any bureau departments. As such, the committee expresses concern.
The Environmental Bureau to set up specific, measurable performance target and timetable for improving shoreline cleanliness, and assign a department to take up the responsibility to ensure the cleanliness of the shoreline areas which do not fall within the purview of any government department.
In conclusion, Mr. President, I wish to record my appreciation on the contribution made by members of the committee. Our gratitude goes to the witnesses who attended the hearing, Health Body Committee. I would like to express my sincere gratitude to the Director of Audit and his colleague for their.